[{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980398406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":13740,"timeElapsed":140520},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980411102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":12694,"timeElapsed":153216},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980420270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9167,"timeElapsed":162384},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":6952,"timeElapsed":169337},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980435246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8021,"timeElapsed":177360},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":10143,"timeElapsed":187504},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980463806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":18415,"timeElapsed":205920},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":7735,"timeElapsed":213656},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980477518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":5975,"timeElapsed":219632},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980494118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":14136,"timeElapsed":236232},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501502,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7382,"timeElapsed":243615},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980510246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":8743,"timeElapsed":252359},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6511,"timeElapsed":258871},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":24783,"timeElapsed":283656},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":13136,"timeElapsed":296792},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980558853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4174,"timeElapsed":300967},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980562110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3255,"timeElapsed":304224},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"181","question":"What is your earliest memory? Do you know how old you were in this memory?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3151,"timeElapsed":307376},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980577741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":11175,"timeElapsed":319855},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980580830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3087,"timeElapsed":322944},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980584141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3311,"timeElapsed":326255},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980588366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":4223,"timeElapsed":330480},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593173,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4806,"timeElapsed":335287},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980598534,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":5359,"timeElapsed":340648},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980601038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2503,"timeElapsed":343152},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980606222,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5184,"timeElapsed":348336},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"61","question":"What part of your everyday life would have seemed magical or impossible to your great-grandparents?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":41550,"timeElapsed":389888},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980658989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":9895,"timeElapsed":401103},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980661022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2031,"timeElapsed":403136},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3647,"timeElapsed":406784},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4071,"timeElapsed":410855},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980674205,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5463,"timeElapsed":416319},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980677406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3199,"timeElapsed":419520},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980681437,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4031,"timeElapsed":423551},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685981,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4543,"timeElapsed":428095},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4472,"timeElapsed":432568},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980702789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":10855,"timeElapsed":444903},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980705165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":2375,"timeElapsed":447279},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980708501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3335,"timeElapsed":450615},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3783,"timeElapsed":454400},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980718005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5719,"timeElapsed":460119},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980730742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":12736,"timeElapsed":472856},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980736749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":6007,"timeElapsed":478863},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980739653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2903,"timeElapsed":481767},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980743286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3632,"timeElapsed":485400},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980752901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8366,"timeElapsed":495015},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980756997,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4095,"timeElapsed":499111},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980760342,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3344,"timeElapsed":502456},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980763341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2998,"timeElapsed":505455},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980767166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":3824,"timeElapsed":509280},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980799982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":32815,"timeElapsed":542096},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980803357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":3375,"timeElapsed":545471},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980805742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2384,"timeElapsed":547856},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980807951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2208,"timeElapsed":550065},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980816333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7311,"timeElapsed":558447},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980821078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4743,"timeElapsed":563192},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980823398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2319,"timeElapsed":565511},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980825701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2303,"timeElapsed":567815},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980828509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2807,"timeElapsed":570623},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980835343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":6832,"timeElapsed":577457},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1614,"timeElapsed":579071},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980839974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3015,"timeElapsed":582088},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980841606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"211","question":"Do you have a favorite TV show or one you watched recently that you particularly enjoyed? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1632,"timeElapsed":583720},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980863742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":11624,"timeElapsed":605856},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980866741,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":2998,"timeElapsed":608855},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980870134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3392,"timeElapsed":612248},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980873549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3414,"timeElapsed":615663},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980875781,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2231,"timeElapsed":617895},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3279,"timeElapsed":621175},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980881461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":2399,"timeElapsed":623575},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980883685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2223,"timeElapsed":625799},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980886141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2455,"timeElapsed":628255},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980895486,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9344,"timeElapsed":637600},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980905421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":7431,"timeElapsed":647535},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980911574,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6152,"timeElapsed":653688},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980918198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6624,"timeElapsed":660312},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980921742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3542,"timeElapsed":663856},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980923941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2198,"timeElapsed":666055},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980925590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1647,"timeElapsed":667704},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980931878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":6287,"timeElapsed":673992},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980934157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2278,"timeElapsed":676271},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980936181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2023,"timeElapsed":678295},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980938597,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"108","question":"What are some pieces of media (books, movies, music, etc.) that have influenced how you think or see the world?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2415,"timeElapsed":680711},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980946645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":6726,"timeElapsed":688759},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980948437,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1791,"timeElapsed":690551},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980953813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":5375,"timeElapsed":695927},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980956533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2719,"timeElapsed":698647},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980962021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":5487,"timeElapsed":704135},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980967197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":5175,"timeElapsed":709311},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980969966,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":2768,"timeElapsed":712080},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980971989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2023,"timeElapsed":714103},{"subjectID":"fl6v8qy6vk","prolificID":"66a7a30a021e287f1f175008","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2675cd56be5911fa939","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980974749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2759,"timeElapsed":716863}]